itsannatopping@gmail.com 603-533-0908

Anna Topping

Hardworking, responsible **Senior Support Engineer** with five years of client and project management experience. Enjoys collaborating with others and enabling teams to reach their highest potential. Not afraid to ask questions because I am always sharpening and updating my skills to incorporate into my daily work.

Experience

Ungork I New York, NY

Senior Support Engineer I July 2021 - Present

- I serve as the highest escalation point for technical support issues within the Global Support Services team.
- Maintain a full working knowledge of Ungork's configuration best practices, new features, and platform capabilities.
- Act as an individual contributor through my independent work creating 10 strategic platform monitors in Datadog and updating three generations of onboarding material. I built my management toolkit mentoring associates and a summer intern.

Configuration Support Engineer I January 2021 - July 2021

- I worked closely with engineers, client partners, and delivery team to support Unqork built applications through the SDLC cycle.
- Expert in Unqork configuration through both my own research as well as hands on experience creating Unqork built tools for internal and external use. I shared my knowledge with my teammates and those outside of the team who seek our guidance

Associate Support Engineer I April 2020 - January 2021

- I used my exceptional problem solving and strong interpersonal communication skills to work with customers and to help resolve their complex Unqork problems.
- I worked directly with over 20 high profile clients including Principal Life, Liberty Mutual, and The City of New York.

Zero-In I New York, NY

Web Project Manager I January 2020 - April 2020

- I worked directly with full stack developers to create new digital marketing solutions for over 50 projects and managed API connections to business management softwares like MindBody, as well as integrations with social media platforms like Instagram and Facebook.
- Managed the entire life 3 high-profile web-based projects with Equinox by communicating with hardware teams, designers, and front end developers.

Digital Account Manager | September 2018 - December 2019

- Manager of 73 mid-size accounts, I led weekly project-update meetings, assessed new content requests, and placated support issues and installation requests.
- Oversaw the workflow for over 30 projects at a time by organizing requirements, timelines, and scope. I worked directly with clients to onboard users to CMS systems and provided excellent customer service with frequent reach outs and check-in video calls.

Education

General Assembly I New York, NY

Javascript Development I Jan 2020 - April 2020

Mastered the fundamentals of JavaScript and advanced APIs to build a full-functional mobile application.

Emmanuel College I Boston, MA I Class of 2017

Bachelor of Arts in English, Communications, and Media Studies

Skills	 Javascript and jQuery 	 Amazon Web Services 	MySQLDatadog	 System Management 	 Attention to detail
	LinuxTesting and debugging	Cloud Computing JIRA and AGILE	MongoDB Database	 A logical approach to work 	Strong communicationConfident technical trainer